what did I really lose that day?
ano hi honto ni ushinatta monotte nan dattakke
for the life of me I can't remember
tou ni wasureteshimatta yo
we slowly lost sight of each other in the twilight
yuugure de futari sukoshizutsu mienakunatteitte
and yet we're stuck here unable to go home
sore nanoni bokura kaerezu ni ita
weak, frail souls lost in the world
dokoka ni kowaresou na moroi kokoro
we act strong to hide their fragility
tsuyogaru kotoba de ootte kakushiteru
＜５年以下の懲役 または➡
hide their fragility
ootte kakushiteru
50万円以下の
罰金に処せられます＞
so farewell, but even forced apart
sayonara aenakunattatte
＜後悔しても 元には戻せない＞
our stories go on
bokura wa tsuzuki ga aru kara
不正視聴!?
even in a world without you, I run
kimi no inai sekai datte hashiru yo
to someday get past the pain
itsuka no itami mo koete
Big Adventure!
The Quest for the Fourth's Legacy - Part 2
(カカシ)なんとか 形になってきたな。
It's starting to take shape.
いや まだだ。
相手は 止まっている岩だからな。
No, not yet.
Considering I'm only aiming
at a motionless rock.
確かに… 本選までに
実践で通用するか➡
That's true...
I wish you could test it to see
whether it will work in a real battle
in the Final Round.
試しておきたいところだな。
これは？
What is this?
いやぁ さっきの大蜘蛛には
びっくりしたよな！
Man, that giant spider was
a surprise!
So why did you dash out
to confront it?
(サクラ)つうか あんた
何 勝手に向かっていってんのよ。
危ないじゃない！
That was so dangerous!
All right, let's beat
the Fourth Hokage's record time
さぁ 四代目の記録を破って➡
その遺産ってやつを
手に入れようぜ！
and find this legacy!
Did you hear what I said?!
人の話を聞け！
Ow! Sakura-chan, that hurts...
Ow, my nose!
痛い。
サクラちゃん これ とっても痛い。
痛い 鼻に… 痛い！
シカマル？
次の関門は この先だ。 先に行け。
Shikamaru?
The next hurdle should
be right up here.
You guys go first.
あんたは どうすんのよ？
What are you gonna do?
俺は ちょっとな。
I have something I have to do.
Just go ahead of me.
You're in a hurry, right?
いいから行け！ 急いでんだろ？
What's with him?
なんだ？ あいつ…。
Yo! Where are you going?
よっ どこ行くんだ？
You fool!
Why are you following me?!
バカ！ お前 何でついてくるんだ？
Well, I wanted to know
where you're going.
だって 気になるし…。
Whoa! What is that?!
おっ 何だ？ あれ！
チッ… 岩に気をとられるな！
Sheesh...
Don't get distracted by a rock!
The enemy... is that shadow!
敵は その陰だ！
Enemy?!
敵～!? うおっ！
死ね～っ!!
Die!
うわぁ～!!
ふぅ…
影真似の術 成功。
Shadow Possession Jutsu
was a success.
危ねえ 危ねえ。
That was close. So close.
Heh! I'll show ya what I can do!
ヘン！ 俺だって
いいとこ見せちゃうもんね！
Multi Shadow Clone Jutsu!
多重影分身の術！
待て！ 影分身…。
Wait!
A Shadow Clone?
They're better than I thought...
こいつら 思ったよりやる！
Retreat!
引け！
ヘヘッ！
(シカマル)お前ら 中忍試験に落ちた
雨隠れの忍だな？
You're the Hidden Rain ninja
who didn't make the Chunin Exam.
目的は何だ？
What is your objective?
目的？ まさか
お前らも 四代目の遺産を…。
Objective?
Don't tell me you guys
are also trying
to get the Fourth's Legacy,
the ultimate secret?!
究極奥義を狙ってんのか？
A-Are you stupid?!
バッ… バカだろ お前！
へ？
Huh?
ったく…
もう 俺たちを狙うんじゃねえぞ。
Cripes! Don't come after us again.
次は ただじゃおかねえぜ。
Next time,
you won't get away with it.
Huh? Hey!
あ… おい！
なんで逃がしちまうんだよ!?
Why'd you let them go?!
You just sowed some
troublesome seeds, again.
お前 また
面倒のタネ まきやがって…。
とにかく今は
やつらに関わってる暇はねえ！
Anyway, we don't have time to
deal with them right now!
We have to beat
the Fourth Hokage's record.
俺たちは四代目の記録を
破らなきゃなんねえんだからな。
シカマル！ 何があったの？
Shikamaru! What happened?
ちょっと ヤボ用がな。
で 次の関門は何だ？
Just a small distraction.
So, what's the next hurdle?
それが… 札が外れちゃって…。
Well... The tag's come off...
We don't have time.
時間がねえ。
とっとと行くってばよ！
Let's just go!
ちょっと ナルト！
Hey, Naruto!
Jeez! We still haven't
deciphered the Tiger Scroll!
もう！ トラの巻の解読は
まだだってのに！
野菊を手向けよ… か…。
"Offer a wild chrysanthemum..."
We're at the next hurdle!
次の関門に到着！
何だ？ これ…。
What is this?
It says, "retire button".
リタイヤボタン… って書いてあるけど。
Come back!
戻れ！ うかつに進むんじゃねえ！
え？
Don't go forward recklessly!
Huh? Huh?
え？ え？
何？ これ…。
What is this?
It's sleeping gas!
(サクラ)睡眠ガスだわ！
くっ！
(チョウジ)うわぁ… 入り口が！
The entrance!
Don't breathe, Naruto!
吸っちゃ駄目よ！ ナルト！
(シカマル)天井へのぼれ！
Climb to the ceiling!
A-Are we locked in?
と… 閉じこめられたの？
There should be a way
to stop this smoke.
《何か
煙を止める方法があるはずだ…。
何か…》
Something...
From up here,
何か 上から見ると
でっけえ花みたいだな。
it looks like a giant flower.
"Offer a wild chrysanthemum..."
《シカマル : 野菊を手向けよ…》
チョウジ！
肉弾戦車で煙を吹き飛ばせ！
Choji! Use your Human Boulder
and blow this smoke outta here!
Then search that hole
under the floor!
床の穴を探るんだ！
了解！
Gotcha!
Expansion Jutsu! Human Boulder!
倍加の術！ 肉弾戦車！
ゴロゴロ…。
Is there anything in that hole?
(シカマル)穴の中に 何かねえか？
ちょっと待って。 え～と…。
Hold on!
Umm...
何か スイッチがあるよ！
There's a switch!
そいつを押すんだ。
うん！
Okay, press it!
Right!
う～ん…。
Thank goodness.
やれ やれ…。
歩けるか？ いの。
えぇ…。
Can you walk, Ino?
Yeah...
出口だってばよ！
An exit!
おぉ 川だ。 道は… こっちか！
Hey, it's a river!
The path is... this way!
Okay, everyone!
よ～し みんな！
俺について来るってばよ！
Just follow me!
Hey, start studying a little.
お前は 少し学習しろ。
何すんだよ。
What're you doing?!
First, the Tiger Scroll.
まずは トラの巻だ。
We can't afford any more mistakes.
もう 間違えようがねえ。
These poem-like phrases contain hints
この巻物の詩みてえなもんが➡
on how to get through
the hurdles.
関門攻略の ヒントになってる。
ふ～ん。
Hmm...
Let's figure out countermeasures
before we find ourselves in a bind.
危ねえ目にあう前に
対処法を考えておこうぜ。
ったく いっつもナルトが先走って➡
Cripes, you're always jumping
the gun
and putting everyone in danger, Naruto!
みんなが危険な目にあうのよね！
Sakura, don't say such a thing...
サクラちゃん… そんなぁ…。
(チョウジ)シカマル
次は何て書いてあんの？
Shikamaru, what's written next?
Yeah...
あぁ。
極めてすばやく 意志を示せ… だ。
"Be extremely nimble,
show determination."
Nimble, eh?
すばやくだな よし！
All right!
(シカマル)ナルト お前… 何すんだ!?
Naruto! What're you doing?!
すばやく意志を
示したんだってばよ！
Nimbly showing determination!
うわっ！
バカ ナルト～！
Stupid Naruto!
しかたねえ 行くぜ！
We have no choice. Let's go!
Weren't you listening earlier?!
あんた さっきの話を
聞いてなかったの!?
Well, I'm just following
the Tiger Scroll.
いや…
俺は トラの巻の言う通りに…。
はぁ。
なんか流れが
早くなってきてない？
Do you feel the current picking up?
I-Is it because of that?
あれのせいじゃない？
- We did it!
(みんな)滝！
We'll crash onto the rocks!
このままじゃ岩に激突しちゃう。
Even if you miss the rocks,
we'll fall under the waterfall.
かわせたとしても
滝の下にまっ逆さまね。
Why are you talking like
an observer?
なによ 人事みたいに。
はぁ？
Huh? I'm just making
a calm assessment!
冷静に判断したまでですけど。
(チョウジ)２人ともやめなよ。
Stop it, both of you!
You should talk!
Start doing something!
あんたこそなんとかしなさいよ！
なんですって？
What?!
Shut up!
うるせえっ！
《くそっ 意志をしめせってのは
何なんだよ》
Damn, what does it mean
by "show determination"?
What's that?
何だ？ あれは。
That rock looks like
a miniature version
あの岩 木ノ葉の顔岩の
ミニチュア版じゃねえか。
of the Hidden Leaf Village's
Great Stone Faces.
なに？
What?
シカマル どうすんのよ？
早くしないとぶつかっちゃうよ。
Shikamaru! What do we do?!
We have to hurry or we'll crash!
意志を示せ… か。
Show determination, huh?
I have determination!
俺の意志は決まってるってばよ。
ナルト。
Naruto...
何が何でも 四代目の遺産を
手に入れてやるんだ！
No matter what, I'm gonna get
the Fourth's Legacy!
ナルト！ あんた何回…。
いや。
Naruto! How many times
do I have to...
No!
This one time, Naruto is right!
Jump to the right!
今回ばかりはナルトが正しい。
右へとべ。
(サクラたち)キャ～ッ！
ぐあっ！ うえっ！
I see...
なるほど 滝の下に
こんな仕掛けがあったのか。
It was set up like this
beneath the waterfall.
飛沫が生まれる左側には
虹ができて➡
A rainbow forms on
the left side with the water spray,
右側にはできなかったってわけだ。
but not on the right side.
If we had chosen the left side,
we'd have been eliminated.
左を選んでいたら
失格になっていた。
Hey, you're heavy!
Hurry up and move!
ちょっと重いじゃないの。
早くどきなさいよ。
はぁ？ 何言ってんの？
(サクラ)私が重いっての？
Huh? What are you saying?
Are you calling me heavy?
You're one to talk!
あんたこそ。
あんたが重いって言ってんのよ。
Yes, I'm calling you heavy,
Ino Pig!
イノブタ！
ふざけんじゃないわよ デコデコ！
Stop kidding around,
Billboard Brow!
This is a fight that has absolutely
nothing to do with me... Nope.
《僕にはまったく関係のない
争いだな うん》
You three are all pretty heavy!
３人とも十分重いってば。
Huh?!
(サクラたち)あ～!?
え～。
- What?!
(サクラ)ったく ナルトったら
デリカシーのカケラもないんだから。
Jeez, Naruto, you don't have
a shred of delicacy.
I pity you, Sakura...
(いの)あんなやつと同じ班なんて
サクラも大変ね。
Being stuck on the same team
with a guy like that.
ほんとよ。
(チョウジ)ほんとよ。
なんで？
That's for sure!
Really!
Wh-Why?
"Final Hurdle"
All right! We're at the final hurdle.
よ～し 来たぜ 最終関門。
Huh?! Ino! You...
え？ いの あんた。
Choji! You...
チョウジ てめえ。
ごめんよ ナルト。
Sorry, Naruto, but we're going
alone from here on.
ここからは僕たちだけで行くよ。
We're taking
the Fourth's Legacy.
四代目の遺産は
私たちだけでいただくわ。
ちょっと 卑怯なんじゃない？
Hey... This is unfair.
僕たち どうしてもシカマルに
勝ち抜いてほしいんだ。
We want Shikamaru to win,
no matter what.
Shikamaru, now's our chance!
シカマル 今のうちに。
くっ。
(チョウジ)シカマル！
Shikamaru!
(シカマル)憎しみを越え
近づくものに道は開かれん。
"Go beyond hatred."
"For the one who approaches,
the path will not open."
That's what the poem says next.
ってのが次の詞だ。
仲間割れなんかしてる者には
道は開かれない➡
Maybe it means the path
won't open
if you have a falling out
with comrades?
ってことなんじゃねえのか？
アハッ。
もっともらしいこと言っちゃって。
Now you're sounding like
a decent guy.
あんた面倒くさくなったわね。
You've really become a pain.
アハハッ シカマルらしいや。
は～。
That's very fitting of you
to say that, Shikamaru.
まぁ こんなことになるとは
思ってたけどね。
Well, I figured it would
turn out like this.
Shikamaru!
シカマル。
あ～？
Huh?
Let's both get through this
and meet in the finals!
お互い勝ち抜いて決勝で会おうぜ。
一応これはお前んだ。 返しとくぜ。
Here, this is yours.
I'm returning it to you.
You actually think
you'll be in the finals?
なに決勝まで行く気に
なってんのよ。
She's right. Sasuke-kun's the one
who will advance.
そうよ。 勝ち進むのは
サスケ君に決まってるじゃない。
Huh?!
え～っ!?
Well, as long as it's someone
from the Hidden Leaf.
まぁ 木ノ葉から
誰かが勝ち抜ければ➡
それでいいんじゃねえの？
そうだよな。
Y-Yeah, that's right.
All right! Let's go!
よ～し いこうぜ！
残念だがな
お前たちは本選には出られない。
Unfortunately...
You guys won't be in
the Final Round.
さっきのようにはいかないぜ。
クックッ…。
You won't be as lucky this time.
(みんな)ほ～っ。
Wow...
(サクラ)これ全部
奥義が書かれた巻物なの？
All these scrolls have
secret techniques written inside?
(シカマル)さあな。
I don't know.
(いの)この中から 本物の奥義書を
探し出さなきゃならないのね。
We have to find the real secret
among these.
(チョウジ)こうしてる間にも きっと
時間は迫ってるんだよね。
And the clock's gonna
be ticking while we do this.
ここに四代目の遺産があるのは
間違いねえんだ！
There's no mistake.
The Fourth's Legacy
is here somewhere!
こうなりゃ 片っ端から開けて…。
Let's open up every one of them!
(シカマル)よせ！
え？
Stop!
これだけの神殿だ。
Look at the size of this
sacred place.
どんなトラップがあるか
わかんねえだろ。
Who knows what kind of trap
has been laid.
むぅ…。
それに たぶん
ここにある巻物は全部フェイクだ。
Besides, the scrolls in here
are all probably fakes.
フェイク？
あぁ。 こんだけ大量の巻物を➡
Fake?
It'll take days to check
this volume of scrolls.
いちいち調べていたら
何日かけても終わんねえぜ。
そんなことしてて とても
四代目の記録なんて破れやしねえ。
We'll never break
the Fourth Hokage's record time.
何かあるはずなんだ…。
There has to be something...
something.
何か方法ってやつが。
Some way...
方法？
A way...
頭を使えってことよ！
バカナルト。
Just use your head!
Stupid Naruto!
あ… サクラちゃん ひどい。
Sakura... That was mean.
バ～カ バ～カ！
Stupid... stupid...
バ～カ バ～カ バ～カ！ バ～カ！
Stupid... stupid... stupid... stupid!
もう許して。
そんなに言わなくっても…。
Stupid... stupid...
Give me a break.
Stop saying that already.
私じゃないわよ。
え？
That's not me!
Huh?
バ～カ バ～カ バカナルト！
Stupid... stupid... stupid Naruto!
てめえか この野郎！
Why you...!
バカオウムなんかに
バカにされる筋合いはねえ！
Stupid parrot!
You have no right to call me stupid!
バカナルト！ バカナルト！
Stupid Naruto! Stupid Naruto!
くっ…
バカにバカって言うんじゃねえよバカ！
Quit saying stupid, stupid!
バカナルト！ バカナルト！
なっ!?
Stupid Naruto! Stupid, stupid!
Why you...!
忍法 うらみ雨。
Ninja Art: Grudge Rain!
一人ひとりの力では
やつらには勝てないが➡
One on one,
we can't beat them.
我らの恨みの念を集めし
呪い術なら…。
But if I gather our grudge and
put a curse on them with a jutsu...
呪いの雲に包まれて
恨みの雨を浴びよ。
Enshroud them
in the cursed cloud...
and rain grudge upon them.
バカナルト バカナルト！
下りてこい！
Stupid Naruto!
- Stupid Naruto!
- Come down from there!
Stupid.
バカオウム！
Stupid parrot!
水？
(いの)シカマル！
Water?
Shikamaru!
(シカマルたち)うわ～っ！
チャ… チャクラが…。
M-My chakra...
《なんだ？
力が抜けてくってばよ》
What's this?
I feel my power draining.
《これは ただの水じゃねえ》
This is... not ordinary water.
この雨は
お前らのチャクラを吸い取る➡
This rain sucks out your chakra.
我らが今まで流し続けた
恨みのこもった涙雨だ。
It is a rain of tears from all
the grudges we hold against you.
中忍試験に落ちたやつらが
コソコソ何してる？
Why are guys like you,
who didn't pass the Chunin Exam,
sneaking around here?
カカシの言いなりになるのも
シャクだが。
Although it is irritating to
do as Kakashi says...
木ノ葉の…。
You're the Hidden Leaf's...
確かに術を試すのには
もってこいだ。
He's right about this being
a perfect chance to test my jutsu.
うちはサスケ！
Uchiha Sasuke!
ひっ… 引け！
R-Retreat!
待て 五月雨！
Wait, Samidare!
やつの様子がおかしい。
He's acting strange...
チャンスじゃないのか？
ちっ 違う！
Isn't this our chance?
N-No!
やっちまおう！
Let's get him!
あ… ぐわ～！
やっぱり 強え…。
He's strong, after all.
本選まで勝ち抜いたやつには
かなわねえ。
We don't have a chance
against someone
who made it through to
the Final Round.
助かった。
これも仕掛けだったのか？
We're saved.
Was this planned too?
もう僕 お腹ペコペコだよ。
I'm starving...
いただきま… あっ 泥棒！
- I'll eat this.
- Gimme, gimme!
- Hey, thief!
- Thank you!
サンキュー！
ナルト！ オウムのほうへ近づいてみろ。
Naruto!
Get close to the parrot!
え？
うまい うまい！
おいしい おいしい！
Huh?
Yummy! Good!
そうか！ 今が
あの憎たらしいオウムを捕まえる➡
I get it. This is my chance to
catch that revolting parrot!
チャンスってことだな。
(シカマル)違う！
No!
Huh?
なるべく笑顔で
親しげに近づくんだ。
Smile a little!
Be friendly as you approach.
な… 何だってばよ？
Wha-? How?
こ こうか？
オウムちゃ～ん こんにちは。
L-Like this?
Little parrot! Hello!
バカナルトか。 バ～カ！
ムカッ！
Stupid Naruto? Stupid!
(シカマル)バカ！ 笑え ナルト。
な… なんで…。
Stupid! Smile, Naruto!
Wh-Why?
笑顔がキモイ。
もっと自然に。
His smile is creepy!
Be more natural!
くぅ～ 勝手なこと言いやがって。
Yeah, it's easy for you to say.
フフ… 何か楽しいことでも
考えてみれば？
サクラちゃん？
Think happy thoughts.
Sakura...
シカマルには何か考えがあるのよ。
Shikamaru must have
something planned.
頑張れ ナルト。
Go for it, Naruto.
サクラちゃんが そう言うなら
頑張ってみるってばよ。 むっ！
If you say so, Sakura,
I'll do my best!
笑顔だ。 微笑みを忘れるな！
Smile!
Don't forget to smile!
(サクラ)そう その調子！
(チョウジ)いいぞ！
Just like that, Naruto!
《楽しいこと 楽しいこと…。
Pretty good!
Happy thoughts...
中忍になったら
サクラちゃんと ラブラブデート》
I'll become a chunin and
go on a lovey-dovey date
with Sakura-chan.
ナハ ナハナハ。
うざっ！
Oh yuck!
エヘヘヘ…。
(シカマル)憎しみを越え
近づく者に道は開かれん。
"Go beyond hatred..."
"For the one who approaches,
the path will not open."
(サクラ)ナルトが オウムを
追いかけまわしてる間は➡
So that meant the gate
wouldn't open
as long as Naruto kept
chasing the parrot.
扉は 開かないって
ことだったのね。
おぉ あった！
四代目の遺産だ！
Oh! Here it is!
The Fourth's Legacy!
最後の詞は
無限のありかを示さん…。
The final lines of the poem...
"The location of infinity,
to the one anointed."
この巻き物に
すべてが示されてるってわけか。
Does that mean this scroll
contains everything?
ああ。 とんでもない
トラップ込みかもしれねえがな。
Yeah... Although there could
be some unthinkable trap.
俺は その虎の巻を信じる。
I believe in that Tiger Scroll!
あのじいちゃん仙人が
くれたんだからな
That old sage gave it to us!
だから怪しいんだろ。
That's why it's suspect.
- Yikes!
Humph...
フォッフォッ フォッフォッ。
ガイ先生！
Guy-sensei!
なんで 先生が！
ここに!?
Why are you...
...here?!
シカマル？ チョウジもいのも
なに言ってんだ？
Shikamaru!
You too, Choji and Ino,
what're you talking about?!
どこに
ゲキマユ先生がいるんだってばよ？
Where is Bushy Brow-sensei?!
- Huh?!
《まだ信じてるんだ ナルト》
You still believe
it's an old sage, Naruto?
なあ 仙人のじいちゃん。
Say, Old Sage! What about it?
どうなんだ？ 俺たち
四代目の記録を破れたのか？
Did we break
the Fourth's record?
間に合ったのか？
Did we make it in time?
どうしても
四代目の遺産がほしいんだ！
I really, really want
the Fourth's Legacy!
本選を突破するために
超 必要なんだってばよ！
I need it in order to get
through the Final Round!
オッホン。
Ahem!
合格！ お前たちは見事
四代目の記録を破ったのだ！
You shattered the Fourth's old record!
やった！
Yay!
それでは 四代目の遺産
究極の奥義を授けよう。
And so... I shall present you
with Fourth's Legacy,
the ultimate secret.
Yeah, yeah!
詞の頭を横に読めじゃ。
Read the first characters of
each verse across the page!
おっと。 健闘を祈る。
I wish you luck!
がんば！ 青春！
Farewell!
バレバレだし。
えっと…。
It was so obvious...
Umm...
刃をおさめ 心を穏やかにせよ。
"Close the blade..."
"Calm the heart..."
刃… 心？
Huh? Blade... heart?
なんだ？
刃に心で忍だろ。
A blade with a heart
means "ninja."
あ そっか。
とすると なになに…。
Oh yeah! Then...
Let's see...
"There is no shortcut to
what is essential in a ninja."
ハァ!?
- Huh?!
ご苦労さん。
おう。
Good work.
Sure thing.
本選突破のための
いい修業になったろ。
It was good training for
passing the Final Round.
こっちもいい感じで
術の完成度を確認できたよ。
And we were able to
assess their mastery
of their jutsu quite nicely.
サスケ あれじゃ術の発動まで
時間がかかりすぎだ。
Sasuke, you're taking too long
to release that jutsu.
本選では通用しないぞ。
わかってる。
It won't be effective
in the Final Round.
I know.
じゃあな ガイ。
まだ サスケの修業が残ってるんでな。
We're leaving, Guy.
Sasuke still needs some training.
うむ。 あとは任せておけ！
Yup! Leave the rest to me!
(いの)なんなのよ チョウジ！
Cripes, Choji!
全部 ガイ先生の
イタズラだったんじゃない！
Does it mean this was all
Guy-sensei's joke on us?!
(チョウジ)そんな～ 僕だって
がっかりしてるんだから。
Well... I'm just as disappointed as you.
悪ふざけで あんな
命がけの仕掛けをするなんて➡
That was so mean laying
such dangerous traps too.
どんだけ暇なのよ。
(シカマル)決めつけんのは➡
Doesn't he have better things
to do with his time?!
Don't be so quick to judge him.
早いんじゃねえか？
え？
いくつもの関門をくぐるうちに
気づかされたじゃねえか。
After passing through
several hurdles,
didn't you notice something?
俺ら 最初は自分たちの
班さえ勝てばいいと思ってた。
At first, we were only thinking
about our team winning.
そうね。
That's true.
今は 里の誰かが
勝ち抜いてくれればって思ってる。
And now, we just want someone
from our village to win.
うん。
Yeah...
わかったってばよ！
(みんな)え？
I know!
- Huh?
忍の極意に近道なし。
There is no shortcut to
what is essential in a ninja!
近道せずに
遠回りをすればよかったんだ。
Don't take the shortcut.
Just take the long way!
よ～し。
サクラちゃん シカマル チョウジ いの！
All right!
Sakura-chan! Shikamaru! Choji! Ino!
もう１回 スタートから
やり直すってばよ！
We're gonna start all over again!
- What?!
やっぱり
めんどくせえやつだ。
He's a pain, after all.
＜カカシ : 中忍試験の本選は
その翌日から始まったのである＞
Stupid! Stupid!
The Final Round of the Chunin Exam
began the next day.
when the fireworks suddenly explode in the air
fui ni agatta hanabi wo futari de miageta toki
I couldn't keep my eyes off from your face
muchuu de miteru kimi no kao wo
I gazed at you quietly
sotto nusumimita no
it'd be so much easier if I was able to hate you
kimi no koto kirai ni naretara ii noni
because I always remember you in situations like this
kyou mitai na hi ni wa kitto
I can't help but think about the times we spent together
mata omoidashiteshimau yo
I'm ready to forget you
mou wasureyou kimi no koto zenbu
it just tears at my heart too much
konna ni mo kanashikute
I wonder why did we meet each other
doushite deatteshimattan darou
when I close my eyes
me wo tojireba
It's like you are here
ima mo kimi ga soko ni iru you de
(エルザ)なんということだ…。
(ナツ)大事な修業期間が…。
Next Episode
I want to hear what you have to say... then decide.
(ハッピー)星霊界で
たった１日過ごしただけで…。
Fine, I will show you our pain.
(グレイ)３か月が
あっという間に過ぎちまった…。
Nagato! This is a waste of time!
(ルーシィ)どうしよう…。
Let's deal with him right now.
(バルゴ)姫！ 提案があります！
Wait, Konan...
I want to hear his answer.
私に もっと きつめのお仕置きを。
He crushed the six Pains and made it here alone.
帰れば…。
Next time on Naruto Shippuden: "Meeting"
Meeting
Two moments define my greatest pain.